Ondřej Paška

randalfien.github.io on.paska@gmail.com +420732749352

Summary

Unity Developer with a solid CS background. More than 5 years of experience with games and multiplatform development. Proficient in C#, JavaScript, and ActionScript 3. Self-motivated, interested in using creative solutions and coming up with game design ideas. Frequent game-jammer.

Experience

Geewa - Unity Programmer

Feb 2019 - now

• Implemented a variety of features in Smashing Four (free-to-play mobile game)

Grip Digital - Unity Programmer

May 2018 - 2019

- Porting games to consoles, optimizing performance, designing controls and GUI
- Worked with Xbox, PS4, Nintendo Switch

Charles Games - Senior Programmer

2012 - now

- Worked with Czech academics on the *Attentat 1942* game, which won the Czech Game of the Year 2017 and the Best Learning Game at Games for Change 2018, and the upcoming sequel *Svoboda 1945*
- Built custom editor tools in Unity, including a custom node-based conversation editor and custom localization tools
- Invited to give a guest lecture to Game Dev students at Charles University about Unity editor scripting (May 2019)
- PC and Mac, C#, Unity, ActionScript 3, Adobe AIR, Java

MathMage - Programmer

2017

- Implemented gameplay features for a math game aimed at young students.
- Android and iOS, Cocos2D, Cocos Creator, JavaScript

Mozkovna – Game Designer, Mobile Developer

2014 - 2016

- Ran the development of a mobile quiz game
- Awarded the Czech Mobile App of the Year 2016 in games category
- Implemented turn-based multiplayer gameplay and monetization, supervised content creators, and managed the community
- Android and iOS, ActionScript 3, Adobe AIR

Other projects and details

Education

Faculty of Information Technology – CTU in Prague • Master's degree, Software Engineering	2013 – 2016
University of Wisconsin in Madison • Study abroad semester	2015
• 3D Graphics, Image Processing	
Faculty of Information Technology – CTU in Prague • Bachelor's degree. Computer Science – Software Engineering	2010 – 2013